mobileacademy.com 2019-05-30

# Privacy Policy – Mobile Academy

This Privacy Policy explains our commitments and your rights concerning your information. You should read the Privacy Policy carefully. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Sites or Services. The Privacy Policy is duly incorporated and subject to the Terms of Service, and governs the same Services and Sites as the ones mentioned in the Terms of Service. Any terms we use in the Privacy Policy without defining them have the same definition given to them in the Terms of Service.

BASICALLY

We wrote this policy to help you understand what information we collect, how we use it and what choices you have about it. Because we’re an internet company, some of the concepts below are a little technical, but we’ve tried our best to explain things in a simple and clear way.

##### WE COLLECT INFORMATION THE FOLLOWING WAYS:

**1\. When you give it to us or give us permission to obtain it**

We may collect information from you in a variety of ways such as your name, email address, phone number and bank account information. You may, however, visit our Sites anonymously if you choose to do so. We will collect information from you only if you voluntarily choose to submit such information to us. You can always refuse to provide these information to us. If you choose to subscribe to a Service from us, we or the mobile operator of your network will collect your information related to the payment for the subscription of our Services. Account and billing information collected by the mobile operator is subject to their respective privacy policies.

BASICALLY

When you subscribe to our services, you give us certain information voluntarily. This can include your name, email address, phone number, bank account information, and any other information you give us.

**2\. We get technical information when you visit our Sites and/or Services**

We may collect technical information about you whenever you visit our Sites or use our Services. Technical information we collect may include the user agent, and technical information about your means of connection to our Site, such as the type of device you use, the device screen size, browser type, geographic location (country only), unique device identifiers, Internet Protocol address, mouse events (movements, location and number of clicks), landing pages, operating system, information about your use of our Services and other similar information.

We also use cookies and other technologies to collect technical information from you. A cookie is a piece of information that is stored on your device’s hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information. For example, we use cookies to store your language preferences or other redundant settings, so you don‘t have to set them up every time you visit our Sites or Services.

BASICALLY

Whenever you use any website, mobile application or other internet services, certain information gets created and logged automatically. The same is true when you use our services or websites. Some of the types of information we collect are log data, device information, and cookie data.

**3\. Our partners and advertisers collect and share information with us**  
We use Google Analytics, a web analysis service of Google Inc. (“Google”) which assists website owners and operators in learning and understanding the usage patterns of visitors who use their websites by collecting information, namely; which individual web pages were visited, how long users spent on the website, which websites referred the most visitors, general geographic location of visitors, and other similar anonymous statistics.

For this reason, Google Analytics may create and store several cookies on your device. Google Analytics does not collect any personally identifiable information by default. Google Analytics collects anonymized IP address or internet connections used by visitors to websites on which Google Analytics has been installed. Google Analytics does not reveal or expose the IP address of visitors to the owners of the website on which Google Analytics is installed.

We also use Google AdWords remarketing services to advertise on third-party websites including Google, to visitors who have previously visited our Sites or Services. The advertisement can be on the Google search results page or a website that has the Google display network implemented. For this reason, third-party vendors including Google may create several cookies on your device.

We also enable Hotjar, an analysis software, by inserting a tracking code within our Sites and Services, which further transmits to Hotjar servers based in Ireland (EU).

This tracking code contacts Hotjar’s servers and provides a script to your device accessing the Site or Service. This script will capture specific data related to your interaction with that particular Site or Service. This information is then sent to Hotjar’s servers for further processing. Through these tools, we receive heatmaps, visitor’s recordings, funnels and form analysis, that help us to provide you with a better experience and service as well as assist us in diagnosing technical problems and analyse user trends.

Hotjar uses cookies to collect technical information including standard internet log information and details of your behavioural patterns when you visit our Sites and Service. This is done to provide you with a better experience, identify preferences, diagnose technical problems, analyse trends and generally to help improve our Sites and Services. Hotjar may also use cookies to record login details on your device. This helps to determine whether a particular device previously visited our Sites or Services so that the login details would not have to be re-entered each time you visit that Site or Service. Hotjar also uses cookies to determine if someone has opted out of being tracked by Hotjar services.

Furthermore, we use Google DoubleClick to advertise based on what’s relevant to a user, improve reporting on campaign performance, and to avoid showing advertisements the user has already seen. For this reason, Google DoubleClick creates several cookies on your device. For example, Google DoubleClick uses cookies to keep a log of which advertisements where shown on which browser. When it’s time to serve an advertisement to a browser, Google DoubleClick can use the browser’s cookies to check which Google DoubleClick advertisements have already been delivered to that particular browser. That’s how Google DoubleClick avoids showing advertisements the user has already seen. In the same way, cookies allow Google DoubleClick to log conversions related to advertisement requests—such as when a user views a Google DoubleClick advertisement and later uses the same browser to visit the advertiser’s website and make a purchase.

BASICALLY

We also get information about you and your activity outside our website and services from our advertisers and other third parties we work with, or other publicly available sources.

Online advertisers or third parties share information with us to measure or improve the performance of our services, or to figure out what kinds of ads to show you.

##### HOW TO PREVENT COOKIE STORAGE AND OPT-OUT?

You may choose to set your web browser to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent.

You can also prevent the collection of your data by Google Analytics by visiting Google Analytics opt-out page and installing the Google add-on for your browser. <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout> or visit <https://www.google.com/settings/ads>to set your settings for Google Analytics, Google AdWords, and Google DoubleClick.

You may opt-out from having Hotjar collect your information when visiting our Sites and Services at any time by visiting [www.hotjar.com/opt-out](http://www.hotjar.com/opt-out) and clicking ‘Disable Hotjar’.

For more details on installing and uninstalling the Google add-on, Google Analytics, Google DoubleClick or AdWords, please visit Google’s website.

##### HOW WE USE COLLECTED INFORMATION

We may use your information for the following purposes:

  * Provide the Service(s) you request;
  * Bill and collect for the Service(s) provided to you;
  * Send you marketing communications;
  * Provide customer care;
  * Protect our rights or property;
  * Enforce the Terms of Service;
  * Comply with legal requirements;
  * To improve our Sites and Services;
  * Respond to your inquiries, questions, and/or other requests; and
  * Respond to court orders, subpoenas or other legal proceedings.

In addition, and for similar reasons, we have a legitimate interest in using your information in the aforementioned ways. It is also fundamental to the nature of the services we provide.

BASICALLY

We use your information to provide our services to you, to show you ads that are relevant, interesting and personal to you, to improve our Site and Services, to comply with legal requirements and to respond to your requests.

##### HOW LONG WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION

We will retain your information for as long as needed to provide our services to you. We will retain your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.

When we no longer need to use your information and there is no need for us to keep it to comply with our legal or regulatory obligations, we will either remove it from our systems or depersonalize it so that we can’t identify you.

BASICALLY

We do not keep your information longer than necessary.

##### HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION

We are concerned with protecting your privacy and data, but we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or guarantee that your information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of any of our industry standard physical, technical or managerial safeguards. We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized or accidental access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your information, transaction information and data stored on our Sites.

However, no method of transmission over the internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. We will continue to enhance our security procedures as new technology becomes available.

Because we operate internationally, your information, including personal information, may be transferred to and made available in the USA and/or any other country than your country of residence. Also in these countries, we take all reasonable care to protect your personal information.

BASICALLY

We work hard to keep your information secure. Because we operate internationally, your information, including personal information, may be transferred to and made available in another country than your country of residence. Also in these countries, we take all reasonable care to protect your information.

##### SHARING YOUR INFORMATION

We share your information with online advertisers and third-party companies that we or they use to audit or improve the delivery and performance of ads or content on websites and apps (for example, through Google Analytics and Google Adwords) as outlined above.

Other than as explicitly described in this Privacy Policy, we will not share personally identifiable information with any third party without your expressed written consent. However, we reserve the right to share the information that we collect with third parties in aggregated and/or anonymous form, and we will not necessarily ask for your permission or even inform you that we are doing so. We may also disclose information that we collect, if required to do so by law or in good faith that disclosure is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process served on us; (2) protect and defend our rights or property; or (3) act in an emergency to protect someone’s safety. Note that we may be required to release personally identifying data in response to lawful requests from public authorities including to meet national security and law enforcement requirements.

BASICALLY

We share your information with online advertisers and third-party companies that we or they use to audit or improve the ads or content on websites and apps (for example, through Google Analytics and Google Adwords).

Any other data is not shared, unless we are forced to.

##### CHILDREN’s PRIVACY

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, we do not knowingly collect or solicit information from anyone under the age of 13. In the event that we learn that we have collected information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us by sending an e-mail to the mail address, as communicated to you on the Sites and/or our Services.

BASICALLY

We do not collect information of children under the age of 13.

##### ACCEPTANCE OF PRIVACY POLICY

By using the Sites or any of our Services, you expressly consent to our collection and use of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the changes on this page. Please check the revision date at the bottom of this page to determine if the policy has been modified since you last reviewed it. Your continued use of any portion of our Site or Services following the posting of the updated Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of the changes.

BASICALLY

By using the site, you agree to this Privacy Policy.

##### TRANSFERRING YOUR INFORMATION

You consent to (i) any transfer of your information outside of your country, including the United States, to a country that does not have the same data protection laws as your country and (ii) the use and disclosure of information about you as described in this Privacy Policy.

BASICALLY

As we operate internationally your information might be transferred and stored outside your home country. You allow us to do that.

##### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We may make changes in our Privacy Policy from time to time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you can always access the latest Privacy Policy.

BASICALLY

We update this Privacy Policy and monitor it well.

##### CONTACTING US

If you do not wish to be informed by email or free messages about our Services, if you wish to receive data we saved about you, if you want your data to be corrected, suspended or deleted, if you have a question about this Privacy Policy, the practices of the Sites, or your dealings with the Sites, please contact us by sending e-mail to [support@mobileacademy.com](mailto:support@mobileacademy.com).

If you are based in the EEA and are of the opinion that we have not complied with data protection laws, you have a right to lodge a complaint with the Data Protection Commission in The Netherlands or with your local supervisory authority.

* * *

_UPDATED: 1 MAY 2018_

BASICALLY

Please contact us in case you want to receive data we saved about you, if want your data to be corrected, suspended or deleted, or if you have any other question.

If you are based in the EEA, you can also complain to a regulator when you think that we haven’t complied with data protection law.
